Guide to the Cornell clippings file, 1940-1989
Cornell clippings file, 1940-1989
- Series I. Subject Files
  - Governance- -University Senate, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Grades, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Grades, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Grades, 1965-1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Grades, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Grades, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Grades, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Handicapped Students At Cornell, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Handicapped Students At Cornell, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Handicapped Students At Cornell, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Handicapped Students At Cornell, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Handicapped Students At Cornell, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Handicapped Students At Cornell, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Handicapped Students At Cornell, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Handicapped Students At Cornell, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Student Activities, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Student Activities, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Student Activities, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Health & Safety Violations, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Health & Safety Violations, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Health & Safety Violations, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Health Services, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Health Services, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Health Services, 1967-1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Health Services, 1978-1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hoaxes, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hoaxes, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hoaxes, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hoaxes, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Holiday Decorations, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Holiday Decorations, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Housing- -Administration, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Housing- -Administration, 1969-1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Housing- -Administration, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Housing- -Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Housing- -Administration, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Housing- -Complaints, Grievances, Protests A, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Housing- -Complaints, Grievances, Protests A, 1968-1978 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Housing- -Complaints, Grievances, Protests A, 1982-1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Housing- -Construction & Plans For Growth, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Housing- -Construction & Plans For Growth, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Housing- -Construction & Plans For Growth, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Housing- -Construction & Plans For Growth, 1967-1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Housing- -Construction & Plans For Growth, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Housing- -Construction & Plans For Growth, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Housing- -Construction & Plans For Growth, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Housing- -Cooperatives, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Housing- -Cooperatives, 1954-1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Housing- -Cooperatives, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Housing- -Cooperatives, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Housing- -Cooperatives, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Housing- -Cooperatives, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Housing- -Cooperatives, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Housing- -Minorities, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Housing- -Minorities, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Housing- -Minorities, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Housing- -Minorities, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Housing- -Minorities, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Housing- -Minorities, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Housing- -Minorities, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Housing- -Minorities, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Housing Dormitories, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Housing Dormitories, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Housing Dormitories, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Housing Dormitories, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Housing Dormitories, 1980-1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (General), 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (General), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (General), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (General), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (General), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (General), 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (General), 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Housing- -Shortages, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Housing- -Shortages, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Housing- -Shortages, 1972-1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Housing- -Shortages, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Housing- -Residential Colleges, 1969-1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Housing- -Residential Colleges, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Housing- -Residential Colleges, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Housing- -Rules & Regulations For Landlords, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Housing- -Rules & Regulations For Landlords, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Housing- -Rules & Regulations For Landlords, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Housing- -Rules & Regulations For Landlords, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Housing- -Rules & Regulations For Landlords, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Housing- -Fees, Rents, Etc., 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Housing- -Fees, Rents, Etc., 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Housing- -Fees, Rents, Etc., 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Housing- -Fees, Rents, Etc., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Housing- -Fees, Rents, Etc., 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (Collegetown), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (Collegetown), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Housing- -Off Campus (Collegetown), 1983-1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Housing- -Rules & Regulations For Students, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Housing- -Rules & Regulations For Students, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Housing- -Rules & Regulations For Students, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Housing- -Special Interest Groups, 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Housing- -Special Interest Groups, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Housing- -Special Interest Groups, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Housing- -Special Interest Groups, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Housing- -Special Interest Groups, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Housing- -Special Interest Groups, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Housing- -Special Interest Groups, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Housing- -Discrimination, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Housing- -Discrimination, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Housing- -Discrimination, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Information And Referral Service, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - International Students, 1950-1988 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - International Programs-Cornell Sponsored, 1964-1988 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Investments, 1968-1975 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Investments, 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Investments, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Investments, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Ithaca Calendar Clocks, 1967-1981 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Judicial System, 1960-1969 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Judicial System, 1970-1987 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Lectures, Seminars, Workshops, Conferences, Etc., 1962-1981 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - A Lectures, Seminars, Workshops, Conferences, Etc., 1982-1989 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Legal Assistance Program, 1968-1979 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Livestock, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Mental Health, 1967-1987 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Military Recruitment & Registration, 1969-1983 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Minorities at Cornell, 1970's-80's (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Minority-Admissions & Applications, 1975-1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - November 11th Committee, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Weapons, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ombudsman, 1969-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Orientation Program, 1966-1988 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Paintings, Sculpture, Etc., 1949-1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Peace Corps At Cornell, 1961-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Services, 1971-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Military Recruitment & Registration, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pollution-Air, Water, Etc., 1966-1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Protests, 1958-1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Protests, 1969-1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Protests, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Protests, 1980-1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Protests-Divestment, 1968-1988 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Protests-Divestment, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Protests-Vietnam War-Carpenter Hall Takeover, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Protests-Vietnam War, 1966-1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Protests-Willard Straight Takeover, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Public Interest Research Group, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Publications-Cornell, 1949-1988 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Radio & T.V.-Cornell, 1950-1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Rating-Cornell, 1951-1988 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Real Estate, 1968-1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Recruitment (Of Students, By Cornell), 1970-1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Recycling Program, 1971-1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Registration of Students, 1970-1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Regulations For The Maintenance Of Public Order, 1969-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Research- -Agriculture & Life Sciences, 1961-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Research- -Arts & Humanities, 1965-1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Research- -Engineering, Math & Space Sciences, 1949-1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Research- -General, 1949-1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Research- -Human Ecology & Nutrition, 1963-1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Research- -Industrial & Labor Relations, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Research- -Industrial & Labor Relations, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Research- -Industrial & Labor Relations, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Research- -Science And Medicine, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Sororities, 1964-1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Spouses, 1960-1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Strikes, 1950-1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Student Code, 1963-1987 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Student Employment And Wages, 1978-1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Student- -Life Academic, 1967-1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Student Life- -Social, 1966-1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Student Life- -Political, 1971-1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Student Organizations- -General, 1947-1988 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Students Organizations-Literary & Academic, 1976-1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Student Organizations- -Music & Art, 1948-1984 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Student Organizations- -Social Service, 1967-1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Student Organizations- -Intercollegiate, 1948-1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Student Organizations- -Agriculture Ecology And Conservation, 1966-1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Student Organizations- -Business, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Student Organizations- -Business, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Student Organizations- -Religious, 1961-1988 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Student Organizations- -Military, 1967-1972 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Students Organizations- -Political, 1965-1988 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - A Student Organizations- -Minorities, 1983-1988 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Student Organizations- -Scientific, 1954-1988 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Student Organizations-Theater & Dance, 1965-1987 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Student Organizations- -Sports & Recreation, 1951-1988 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Student Records, 1969-1988 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Summer Session Programs, 1966-1988 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Teachers & Teaching, 1960-1988 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1968-1988 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Telephone Service, 1951-1988 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Tests & Testing, 1969-1981 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Traditions, 1949-1966 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Traditions, 1967-1988 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Traditions- -Hotel Ezra Cornell, 1951-1988 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Transportation, 1966-1986 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Tuition Fees, 1965-1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Tuition, Fees, 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Tuition, Fees, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Tuition, Fees, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Unions And Unionization, 1966-1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - University Relations, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - University Relations, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Visiting Professors & Scholars, 1952-1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Volunteerism, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Women At Cornell, 1969-1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Unions And Unionization, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - A Unions And Unionization, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - A Union And Unionization, 1972-1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Series II. Building Files
  - Administrative & Non-Academic Buildings (A-M), 1951-1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Administrative & Non-Academic Buildings (N-Z), 1950-1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Aeronautical Laboratory, 1950-1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Africana Studies & Research Center, 1968-1988 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, N.Y. State (Geneva), 1958-1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Agriculture & Life Sciences, N.Y. State College Of (1953-1975) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Agriculture & Life Sciences, N.Y. State College Of (1976-1988) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Agriculture & Life Sciences, N.Y. State College Of- -Departments, 1963-1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Agriculture & Life Sciences, College of- -Buildings, 1968-1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Agriculture and Life Sciences, College of- -Buildings, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Anabel Taylor Hall, 1948-1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory (Puerto Rico), 1960-1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Architecture Art And Planning, College of, 1952-1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Arts & Sciences, College of, 1954-1988 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Arts & Sciences, College of- -Depts. (American Studies to English), 1948-1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Arts & Sciences, College of- -Depts. (Geological Sci. to Physics Dept.), 1959-1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Arts & Sciences, College of- -Buildings, 1967-1986 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Arts & Sciences, College of- -Depts. (Psychology to Women's Studies), 1951-1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Biological Sciences, Divisions of- -Buildings, 1966-1986 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Boyce Thompson Institute For Plant Research, 1973-1988 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Biological Sciences, Division of, 1951-1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Campus Life, Division of, 1971-1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Career & Placement Center, 1960-1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - CTR For Agricultural Biotechnology, 1983-1988 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Center For Religion, Ethics & Social Policy, 1976-1987 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Center For Theory & Simulation In Science & Engineering, 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Committee On Special Education Projects, 1963-1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Committee On Special Education Projects, 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Computer Services, Office of, 1959-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Biotechnology Institute, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Institute For African Development, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Institute For Public Affairs, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Institute For Social & Economic Research, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Institute For Social & Economic Research, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Plantations, 1949-1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Exercises at the opening of the Library Building, 1891 (Box 8)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -General, 1950-1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Annex, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Annex, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Annex, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Engineering, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Hotel, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Kroch Library, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Physical Plant Operations, Dept. of, 1969-1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Law, 1961-1983 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Olin, 1961-1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -University Libraries, Pre 1962 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -M.B. Catherwood Industrial & Labor Relations, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -M.B. Catherwood Industrial & Labor Relations, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University Libraries- Music, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Sibley Fine Arts, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Uris Undergraduate, 1962-1980 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Uris Undergraduate, 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Uris Undergraduate Library, Academic Resources Center, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Cornell United Religious Work, 1958-1985 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Cornell United Religious Work- -Civitas, 1968-1988 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Cornell University Libraries- -Special Collections, 1948-1988 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Engineering, College of, 1974-1988 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Engineering, College of- -Departments (A through H), 1968-1988 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Engineering, College of- -Departments (I through Z), 1968-1986 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Engineering, College of- -Buildings, 1951-1987 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - General Services, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - General Services, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Home Economics, N.Y. State College of, 1962-1968 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Hotel Administration, School of, 1962-1988 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Hotel Administration, School of- -Buildings, 1950-1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Human Affairs Program, 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Human Ecology, N.Y. State College of, 1969-1988 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Human Ecology, College of- -Buildings, 1960-1988 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Industrial & Labor Relations, N.Y. State School of, 1962-1988 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Industrial & Labor Relations, N.Y. State School of- -Buildings, 1950-1962 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Interdisciplinary Centers, Programs & Institutes, 1969-1988 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Johnson Art Museum, 1968-1988 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Laboratories, 1951-1983 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Law School, 1953-1988 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Law School- -Buildings, 1964-1988 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Management, Graduate School of, 1955-1988 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC), 1960-1986 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Management, Graduate School of- -Buildings, 1958-1977 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Media Services, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Media Services, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Medical College (New York City), 1951-1988 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Medical College (N.Y.C.)- -Buildings, 1952-1985 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Northeast Dairy Promotion And Research Center, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1954-1985 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Performing Arts Center, 1982-1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Physical Education & Athletics, Dept. of, 1976-1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Physical Education & Athletics, Dept. of- -Buildings, 1949-1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Public Affairs, Division of, 1964-1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Radio Physics And Space Research, Center for, 1964-1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Research Park, 1951-1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Safety & Security, Division of, 1960-1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Schoellkopf Field & Hall, 1968-1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Sapsucker Woods, 1975-1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Shoals Marine Laboratory, 1971-1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sea Grant College, 1942-1995 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Society for the Humanities, 1965-1986 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Statler Club, 1950-1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Synchrotron Laboratory Complex, 1948-1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Sage Chapel, 1956-1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - University Press, 1948-1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - University Unions, Dept. of- -General, 1972-1986 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - University Unions, Dept. of- -Noyes Center, 1964-1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - University Unions, Dept. of- -North Campus Union, 1971-1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Veterinary Medicine, New York State College of, 1952-1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - White Art Museum, 1951-1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - University Unions, Dept. of- -Willard Straight Hall, 1951-1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)